Preliminary Guide to the Frank Smith, Jr. papers, 1992-1998 MS2182
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Frank Smith, Jr. papers
1987-1998
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Smith, Frank Jr.
MS2182
41.5 Linear Feet
These are the office records for Frank Smith Jr. durng his time as a member of the District of Columbia City Council. The records date from 1987-98.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Frank Smith Jr., 1998
Biographical Note
Frank Smith Jr. (1942- ) served as a member of the District of Columbia City Council from 1982-1998. During his time on the Council Smith supported legislation creating subsidies for housing down payments, a lottery system for disposing of condemned and surplus housing and establishing tax incentives for new business development. In 1998, Smith became chairman for the board and chief executive officer for the organization which worked to establish the African American Civil War Memorial and accompanying museum.
During his college days at Morehouse College in Atlanta, Smith was a founding member of the Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee (SNCC). From 1962-68 he worked with SNCC organizing and registering African-American voters in Mississippi and Alabama. In 1968 he moved to Washington and began work as a researcher for the Institute for Policy Studies focusing on education and planning issues.
Frank Smith Jr. was born on September 17, 1942 in Newnan Georgia. He earned a Ph.D from the Union Institute in Ohio in 1980.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains the office records of Frank Smith Jr. during his time as a member of the District of Columbia City Council. These files cover the subjects such as housing, crime, education, lottery, correspondence from constituents, and the Civil War Memorial. These records date from 1987-98. Please note: these records are not fully processed and may take more time to use for research.
Collection Organization
This collection is not fully processed and series have not been determined.
African Americans; Washington (D.C.); City council members -- Washington (D.C.); District of Columbia. City Council; Smith, Frank Jr.; African American Civil War Memorial Freedom Foundation & Museum
- Metropolitan Police Department (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Third District (Box 1, Folder 2)
- DC Auditor Report, 09/30/1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Police correspondence, 03/1995-01/1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Tennant Assistance Program (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 1300 Block Kenyon Street (Box 1, Folder 6)
- DC Assessment Directory, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 1400 Block Chapin, NW (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Clifton Terrace (Box 1, Folder 9)
- BC Art Gallery (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Parking (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Black History Month, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneaous (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Civil War (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Fundraising Activities Events (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Fundraising (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Roosevelt Apartments (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Scattered sites (Box 1, Folder 18)
- ANC Commissioner (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Roosevelt Apartments (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Charlene Drew Jarvis (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Community Folder (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Scheduling (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Advisory Neighborhood Commissioners manual, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Building Plans - 10th and U Street, NW (Box 1, Folder 25)
- MLK Day (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Frank Smith newsletter (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Newsclips (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Step Fast/Garnet-Paterson middle school (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Liberian Support Gorup (Box 1, Folder 30)
- African American Civil War Memorial (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Misc. correspondence (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Frank Smith schedules/info (Box 1, Folder 33)
- DC Map (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Washington Hilton and Towers (Box 1, Folder 35)
- NC Genealogical Society Journal, 11/1995 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Civil War Memorial Project (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Civil War Soldiers System - Packet B (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Civil War Soldiers System - Packet C (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Civil War Soldiers System - Packet D (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Civil War Soldiers System - Packet E (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Civil War Soldiers System - Packet F (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Civil War Soldiers System - Packet G (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Civil War Soldiers System - Packet I (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Civil War Soldiers System - Packet J (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Civil War Soldiers System - Packet K (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Civil War Soldiers System - Packet L (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Civil War Soldiers System - Packet A (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Civil War Soldiers System - MF 19 Packet A (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Civil War Soldiers System - MF 19 Packet B (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Civil War Soldiers System - MF 19 Packet C (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Civil War Soldiers System - MF 19 Packet D (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Civil War Soldiers System - MF 19 Packet E (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Civil War Soldiers System - MF 19 Packet F (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Civil War Soldiers System - MF 19 Packet G (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Civil War Soldiers System - MF 19 Packet H (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Civil War Soldiers System - MF 19 Packet I (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Civil War Soldiers System - MF 19 Packet J (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Civil War Soldiers System - MF 19 Packet K (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Civil War Soldiers System - MF 19 Packet L (Box 2, Folder 18)
- DC Department of Public Works (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Legislation transmittals (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Committee Reports, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- City Council - hearings, testimony, reports (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Partnership for Special Initiatives (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Washington Counci of Agencies - Catalog of Services, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Services for the Homeless, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Metropolitan Washington Regional Directory, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- HMO Provider Directory, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- HMO Provider Directory, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Task Force on DC Governance, 04/1997 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Golden Washington Club directory (Box 3, Folder 8)
- DC Building Industry Association Membership directory, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Ward 1 Plan - draft, 12/1987 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- GAO Report to DC Mayor, 03/09/1983 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Summary of EIS for HOTD System, 01/04/1996 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- DC Capital Plan - improvements and budget requests, 1995-2001 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Appreciation Luncheon for Garnet-Patterson Middle School, 08/31/1995 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- List of Assessed Values, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Advisory Neighborhood Commissioners Manual, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Advisory Neighborhood Commissioners Manual, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Directory of HIV/AIDS Services, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Local business info (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Greater Washington Dental Services (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Community meetings (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Constituent correspondence (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Ward 1 crime (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Staff assignments (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Staff assignments (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Constituent services (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Constituent correspondence (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Latino projects (Box 4, Folder 4)
- PSA list of Ward One (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Rent control information (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Charter school list (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 8)
- ANC - certificate of oath (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Forum event (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Event in Ward One (Box 4, Folder 11)
- January events, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Events - 1st, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Events - 3rd, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Events - 4th, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Events - 6th, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Events - 7th, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Events - 8th, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Events - 9th, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Events - 10th, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Events - 11th, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Events - 12th, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Events - 13th, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Events - 14th, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Events - 16th, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Events - 17th, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Events - 18th, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Events - 19th, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Events - 20th, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Events - 22nd, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Events - 23rd, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Events - 24th, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Events - 25th, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Events - 26th, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Events - 27th, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Events - 28th, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Events - 29th, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Events - 30th, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- DC Wireless Telecom Coalition testimony, 06/24/1998 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Don't Tax Food Coalition (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Grocery Manufacturers of America (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Committee on Finance and Revenue (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Tax Revision Commission Hearing - Part 2 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Tax Check off (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Tax increment financing (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Tax Revision Commission (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Columbia Heights Redevelopment (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Rent control (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Regulatory/Reform (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Public School Accountability Act (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Prostitution legislation - hearing (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Police Department standards (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Police issues (Box 5, Folder 11)
- National Capital Revitalization Corporation (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Metro construction in Columbia Heights (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Lobbying - Asian/Korean community (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Housing and Community Development (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Health and Human Services - Howard University Hospital (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Hearings on Tax Bills (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Grants management (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Employees Residency Incentive Tax Credit Act, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Endorsement Questionnaires (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Frank Smith bio (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Constituent services (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Committee of the Whole public roundtable, 07/28/1998 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- PSA letter and constituent file (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Nurses Association DCNA (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Constituent services (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Legislation, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Constituent file (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Board of Zoning (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Adams Morgan clinic file (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Surveys (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Special Committee on Police Misconduct, 07/17/1998 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Constituent postcards (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Special Committee on Police Misconduct, 06/30/1998 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Committee on Finance and Revenue - OTR spending (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Committee on Finance and Revenue - Smith materials (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Committee on Finance and Revenue - Mark Sobo (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Committee on Economic Development - Public Roundtable (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Legislative materials (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Press (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Smith info (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 24)
- DC Auditor Report, 06/01/1998 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Newsletter - story data (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Committee on Finance and Revenue, 06/24/1998 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Tax Policy letter (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Committee on Finance and Revenue, 07/1998 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Legislative meeting - Mark Sobo, 05/05/1998 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Legislative meeting - Mark Sobo, 06/16/1998 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Legislative meeting - Frank Smith, 06/30/1998 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Legislative meeting - Frank Smith, 07/30/1998 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Legislative meeting - Mark Sobo, 07/07/1998 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Legislative committee meeting - Frank Smith, 07/07/1998 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Committee on Finance and Revenue - Smith, 05/19/1998 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Committee of the Whole - Regular meeting, 05/19/1998 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Committee on Finance and Revenue - OTR Spending (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Council of District of Columbia, 07/30/1998 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Committee on Finance and Revenue - Budget Hearing, 03/05/1998 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Committee on Finance and Revenue - Mark up, 03/26/1998 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Committee on Finance and Revenue - OTR Spending (Box 7, Folder 13)
- DC Tax Revision Commission summary report, 06/1998 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Public appearances (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Rent control (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Homicide division press conference, 10/01/1997 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Invoice (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Banneka High student assault (Box 8, Folder 1)
- CM's car (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Ready, Willing and Able (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Copies of Letters (Box 8, Folder 4)
- The Waldron (Box 8, Folder 5)
- STEP Foundation (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Meetings on Expiring Sec. 8 Certificates (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Ward One Properties with Expiring Sec. 8 Certificates (Box 8, Folder 8)
- La Casa shelter (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Howard University properties (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Columbia Heights village (Box 8, Folder 11)
- CAG (Box 8, Folder 12)
- 1412 Chapin St., NW (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Memos (Box 8, Folder 14)
- 1424 Chapin St., NW (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Metro (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Deaths of Women in Ward One (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Public work (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Police redistricting hearing (Box 8, Folder 19)
- DC Plans (Box 8, Folder 20)
- CWM response letters (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Old Children's Hospital site (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Misc. (Box 8, Folder 23)
- 1828 Investment Club (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Committee on Public Works - Budget Hearing, 01/17/1996 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Staff - Legislation (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Clean up (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Virginia Housing (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Housing Inspection Project (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Arts (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Jubilee Housing (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Cartwright and Riley (Box 8, Folder 32)
- VA Communication clinic (Box 8, Folder 33)
- ANC Listing, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Corporate sponsor returns (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Tri-school Learning Academy (Box 8, Folder 36)
- HORA (Box 8, Folder 37)
- DPW blank complaint forms (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Complaints (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Metro lawsuit (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Park road (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Crime (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Tickets (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Redevelopment Land Agency BoD (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Roosevelt (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Clifton Terrace (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Health articles (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Personal file (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Projects - current (Box 8, Folder 49)
- Letters (Box 8, Folder 50)
- Police service areas (Box 9, Folder 1)
- John W. Brooks (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Misc. (Box 9, Folder 3)
- 440 Manor Place (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Public works (Box 9, Folder 5)
- DCRA (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Civil War memorial (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Breakfast meeting, 07/27/1992 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Mailing lists (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Listings - contacts (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Business lists (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Citizen lists (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Birthday party information (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Christmas RSVP listing (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Directories of Churches and Religious Organizations (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Campaign finance (Box 9, Folder 16)
- CM Birthday Sponsor/Patron list, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Toys for Tots (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Chrismas Party (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Frank Smith testimonial dinner (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Newsletter (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Ward One newsletter (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Newsletter, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Baseball (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Misc. (Box 9, Folder 25)
- The Block (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Legislative Assistant Committee on Judiciary, 01/11/1994 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- ANC (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Department of Human Services (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Misc. (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Policing for Prevention (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Working file - legislation (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Government contact (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Committee on the Judiciary, 07/09/1997 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Redesigning Police beats (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Police (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Judiciary committee, 10/10/1997 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Committee on the Judiciary - Mark up, 10/08/1997 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- First district (Box 10, Folder 5)
- 4th District Police Citizen's Advisory Council (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Committee on Finance and Revenue (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Tax Rev. Comm. Reports, 12/09/1997 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Committee on Finance and Revenue (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Committee on Finance and Revenue (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Committee on Finance and Revenue (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Legislative Meeting [1/2], 04/07/1998 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Legislative Meeting [2/2], 04/07/1998 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Legislative Meeting - Mark Sobo, 10/06/1998 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Legislative Meeting - Mark Sobo, 11/04/1997 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Proposed New Convention Center Projects, 09/1997 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Finance and Revenue Committee (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Committee on Finance and Revenue - DC Lottery (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Finance and Revenue Committee (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Public Roundtable on Grants Management, 11/12/1997 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Markup, 11/25/1997 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Dept. Finance an drevenue - Exempt Organizations Report, 03/16/1995 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Study of Property, Income and Sales Tax exemptions, 04/07/1995 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Taxation Committee - Intergovernmental Relations (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Homestead Exemption Forms (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Committee on Economic Development (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Committee on Economic Development (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Human Services (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Committees on Human Services (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Office of Chief Medical Examiner, 03/10/1998 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Legislative Meeting - Councilmember Smith, 03/31/1998 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Committee on Human Services (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Committee on Human Services (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Committee on Human Services, 03/25/1998 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Committee on Human Services, 03/25/1998 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Commission on Mental Health Services, 07/25/1998 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Committee on Local, Regional, and Federal Affairs (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Local, Regional, and Federal Affairs, 03/10/1998 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Committee on Government Operations (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Committee on Government Operations, 03/16/1998 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Committee on the Judiciary (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Committee on Consumer and Regulatory Affairs (Box 12, Folder 7)
- DCRA Budget Hearing, 03/12/1998 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Committee on Consumer and Regulatory Affairs (Box 12, Folder 9)
- CPWE Public Hearing, 03/25/1998 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Committee on Consumer and Regulatory Affairs (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Legislative Meeting - Committee, 10/07/1997 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Legislative Meeting - Committee, 01/03/1998 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Legislative Meeting - Councilmember Smith, 01/03/1998 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Legislative Meeting - Mark Sobo, 08/24/1998 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Legislative Meeting - Committee, 03/03/1998 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Legislative Meeting - Committee, 09/08/1997 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Legislative Meeting - Councilmember Smith, 09/08/1997 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Comm. On Finance and Revenue, 12/16/1997 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Legislative Meeting - Committee, 01/06/1998 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Finance and Revenue Oversight Hearing, 01/20/1998 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Committee on Finance and Revenue, 04/07/1998 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Committee on Finance and Revenue - Markup, 04/23/1998 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Committee on Finance and Revenue - OTR spending, 03/24/1998-04/07/1998 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Tax Related clippings (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Comm on Finance and Revenue - Tax check off, 05/11/1998 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Lottery - Letters to Mayor (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Lottery Board Public Hearing, 11/28/1995 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Lottery - Reports (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Lottery Board - General (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Committee on Economic Development (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Committee on Economic Development (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Comm on Econ Development - Budget Hearing, 03/09/1998 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Tax Revision Commission (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Comm on Finance and Revenue, 12/09/1997 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Comm on Finance and Revenue reports (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Tax Revision Commission (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Tax Revision Commission (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Tax Revision Commission - Hearing 1, 11/26/1997 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Tax Credits Housing (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Chief Financial Officer (Box 14, Folder 1)
- DC Tax Revision Commission - Summary Report to DC Mayor, 06/1998 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Rent Control (Box 14, Folder 3)
- DC Tax Revision Commission, 11/05/1997 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Management Report [1/2] (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Management Report [2/2] (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Legislation notes (Box 14, Folder 7)
- DC Tax Revision Commission - Fifteenth Meeting, 01/09/1998 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Tax Revision Commission reports (Box 14, Folder 9)
- DC Tax Revision Commission - Fourteenth Meeting, 01/20/1998 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Committee of the Whole (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Committee of the Whole - Regular Meeting, 03/17/1998 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Committee of the Whole, 03/05/1998 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Committee of the Whole, 01/20/1998 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Committee on Public Works and the Environment (Box 14, Folder 15)
- CPWE - Budget Hearing, 03/11/1998 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Committee on Education, Libraries & Recreation (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Committee on Education, Libraries & Recreation (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Reports for Comm on Educ, Lib, & Rec (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Education File (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Education, Libraries & Recreation Public Roundtable, 04/15/1997 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Education File (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Education, Libraries & Recreation Public Oversight Roundtable, 09/26/1997 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- University of DC (Box 15, Folder 8)
- State Education Technology Plan (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Committee on Education Libraries & Recreation (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Committee on Education, Libraries & Recreation - Budget Request, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Ward 1 VIP list, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Calendar (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Ward 1 VIP List, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Minor League Baseball employment guide (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Redevelopment & Revitalization Issues and Options, 10/06/1994 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Youth baseball (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Hellman Company (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Directory of HIV/AIDS Services, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Adams Morgan Day festivities (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Ward One ANC Briefing, 01/18/1997 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- ANC Commissioners (Box 16, Folder 11)
- ANC (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Civil War Memorial (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Comp Forms (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Housing, Juveniles (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Going Back to Mississippi (Box 16, Folder 17)
- 5K Race (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Special Events Task Group (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Thanksgiving Luncheon (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Toys for Tots (Box 16, Folder 21)
- VIP Labels (Box 16, Folder 22)
- WC PCP Dedication Ceremony (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Time Sheets (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Georgia Cafe (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Restoration Cooperative Association, 11/13/1993 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 9)
- UIP Papers (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 14)
- DCRA - Mark-up, 04/09/1998 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Committee of the Whole - Regular Meeting, 04/21/1998 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Committee on Finance & Revenue - Mark-up, 04/23/1998 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Committee of the Whole - Public hearing, 04/28/1998 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Legislative Meeting, 05/05/1998 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Committee of the Whole - Additional meeting, 05/05/1998 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Committee on Finance & Revenue, 05/07/1998 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Committee on Education, Libraries & Recreation, 05/07/1998 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- DCRA - Mark-up, 05/12/1998 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- DCRA - Mark-up, 05/12/1998 (Box 18, Folder 10)